#### Contact

abc 9110197384 (Mobile) ashujha0994@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ashu-jha9g (LinkedIn) github.com/ashutosh123ashu (Other) leneutron.com/ (Blog)

#### Top Skills

Git

**Jenkins** 

Docker

#### Certifications

Certified SAFe 4 DevOps Practitioner

**Devops Professional** 

# Ashutosh jha

DevOps Engineer | AWS | Docker | Kubernetes | Terraform | Jenkins Gurugram, Haryana, India

## Summary

DevOps Engineer with overall 3.8 years of IT experience, coordinating the efforts of product design and development with more business operations.

Currently working with Infosys as Technology Analyst. Working with DevOps team to manage implementation of enterprise applications using orchestration tools like git, Jenkins, docker, Kubernetes.

Following Agile methodology to implement the project. Team builder with strong analytical & interpersonal skill.

I have hands-on experience with Azure cloud platform, BOARDS, AZURE PIPELINES.

## Experience

Persistent Systems
DevOps Engineer
September 2024 - Present (1 year)
Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Infosys
3 years 10 months

Technology Analyst

April 2024 - October 2024 (7 months)

Gurugram, Haryana, India

Technology Analyst February 2024 - October 2024 (9 months)

Senior System Engineer October 2022 - April 2024 (1 year 7 months) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India System Engineer January 2021 - October 2022 (1 year 10 months) Banglore

## Education

### ARYA COLLGE OF ENGINEERING AND I.T.

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2016 - 2020)